Waste another second
Just to get back to the same place
Always running to you
When I’m falling out my headspace
It’s strange
Maybe you should change lanes
Save face, cause you know you
Slept at his place
You can say what you want
But now I’m calling your bluff
Can’t believe you let me
Hide the truth
Taking all the pressure away
It’s like a whole damn bottle
Couldn’t numb all the pain
I guess it’s my fault that you’re feeling this way
Yeah it’s too much and I can’t catch a break
Cause I can take it right back
To the moment we met
And I remember each word
That you said when you left
And I really don’t think
I can stomach the mess
In my head
Play it over again
It’s like, I don’t want let go
Of the love that we had
It doesn’t even make sense
That I left you on read
And believe me I know
I can’t handle the truth
But I can take right back, take it right back to you
Your ghost lives on in the corner room
And I just can’t take it anymore
Burned the pictures of you
Just to settle the score
And my
Mind’s still a little sore
You walked out of that room
Not expecting a war
It’s like a
Bad dream sent to bring me rest
I took another just to clear my head
Seeing shadows in your silhouette
Have I noticed I’m not breathing yet
Taking all the pressure away
Down that whole damn bottle
Finally numbed all the pain
I saw life change over night in way
But it’s too much, and I’m starting to break
Cause I can take it right back
To the moment we met
And I remember each word
That you said when you left
And I really don’t think
I can stomach the mess
In my head
Play it over again
It’s like, I don’t want let go
Of the love that we had
It doesn’t even make sense
That I left you on read
And believe me I know
I can’t handle the truth
But I can take right back, take it right back to you
Taking all the pressure away
Down that whole damn bottle
Finally numbed all the pain
I saw life change over night in way
But it’s too much, and I’m starting to break